Ikraam Chohan

Summary

I am currently a sophomore at the University of Illinois in Chicago Pursuing a bachelor's degree in business administration. I am looking for a job in the business finance field to gain some experience and compliment my education. I am a devoted, hard-working team player committed to reaching my goals and to help you reach yours.

Skills

Bilingual with English and Urdu, 4 years of spanish courses, Computer skills(including Microsoft), customer service, cash handling and balance, problem solving, communication

Education

Lake Park High School District 108 — High School Diploma
August 2016 - May 2020, Roselle, IL

University of illinois at Chicago - Pursuing Bachelor's Degree

Double Major: Information and Decision Sciences; Finance

Experience

Mutual Realty - Office Intern (Aug. 2018 - Sept. 2019) (Jan. 2021-Present)

- Maintained Financial Accounts of Properties on Microsoft Excel
- Organized Property Folders in Microsoft Office and on a Server
- Keep office clean and organized
- Assisted manager with daily tasks
- Did financial research on a number of different properties and came up with bidding amounts for Auctions
- Performed Bank Deposits and Helped Finance manager with Banking
- Did Tax research on Properties

Dunkin' -Staff (May 2020 - May 2021)

- In charge of keeping records and logs of different equipment and food
- Handling and counting cash on a daily basis
- Making food/drinks and handling customers' comments and complaints
- Providing top-notch customer service

Itasca Park District -Lifequard (May'19- Sept'19)(May'20- Sept.'20)

- CPR And First Aid Certified LifeGuard
- Cleaning and maintaining the facility on a daily basis
- Ensured everyone at the facility was safe and taken care of
- Taught different swim and lifeguard classes

Alexian Brothers Hospital -Front Desk Volunteer (Feb.2019- Mar. 2020)

- looked up patient information and maintained confidential information
- Assisted visitors with questions, in person and over the phone